phdessay.com 2005-04-03

# EssayEdge.com: Personal Statement and Admissions Essay Help, Application Essay Editing

**Privacy Policy**

This privacy statement is designed to help you understand how we use and safeguard the personal information you provide to us. This privacy statement describes the practices of cyberedit.com, essayedge.com, resumeedge.com, termpaperedge.com, and webresume.com, members of the Thomson Learning family of companies.

Please note that this website provides direct links to various sponsor and marketing partner sites, where you can apply for products and services (such as student loans) or register for more information. This privacy statement does not describe the practices of our partners. Before disclosing personal information on any other company's web site, you should read the privacy policy associated with that site. 

**Information That We Collect**

When you visit our Web site, you may provide us with information in different ways. For example, you may register with us or sign up for our newsletter. Or, you may complete search forms to get information from us about things like colleges or financial aid. Additionally, we collect information on an aggregate basis as you and others browse our web site. 

The types of information we ask for varies with the search you're conducting. In addition to your name and contact information, we will ask for other information related to the topic. For example, in order to personalize your search for a college, we may ask about your high school graduation date, school performance, desired college locations, and career goals. If you request document editing services from us, you will provide a copy of the letter, essay or resume you want us to revise.

**How We Use the Information**

In general, we use the information you provide in order to:

  * respond to your requests for information
  * provide the services you request
  * provide customer service 
  * provide links between targeted product and service providers and appropriate individuals 

For example, if you request information on financial aid, we will send you that information. If you so choose, we can also provide your information to those marketing partners who offer financial aid packages so they may send you information on their products and services. 

If you request editing or resume writing services, we provide those services and bill you for the services as instructed. We do NOT sell any personal information from essays or resumes to any third parties. For example, unlike some resume services, we do not sell resume information to job posting boards. The full policy regarding use of customer information can be found in the Terms of Service that you must check to complete your order.

If you purchase a product or service on our site, you may provide us with a credit card number. This credit card number will only be used to process your purchase. We will not disclose credit card numbers to third parties for marketing purposes under any circumstances. 

In general, it is our policy to share information with other companies in the Thomson family (such as other Thomson Learning companies) unless you tell us not to by opting out. Unless you agree (by opting in), we will not share personal information about you with unrelated companies except as needed to complete your transaction. However, we may disclose any information when legally compelled to do so or when needed for the protection of our legal rights. For example, we may disclose information about you in response to a subpoena or government investigation. We may also disclose information about you in connection with the transfer of assets of our business.

At registration, you will be given the opportunity to opt-out of internal promotions, offers and marketing messages. You will also be given the opportunity to opt-in to receive offers from partners and third parties.

**Your Choices**

_Opting Out of Offers from Thomson Learning_

We only want to send you information if you want to receive it. You may opt out of receiving additional or future information from us or from having your information shared within the Thomson family at any time by doing any one of the following: clicking the "unsubscribe" link found in every newsletter or email, or by contacting our customer services department by email at [support@essayedge.com](mailto:support@essayedge.com) or phone (1-800-225-0261) and requesting removal from our internal email lists.

_Opting In for Offers from Our Marketing Partners_

If you want to receive information from our marketing partners, you may opt in during the registration process by checking the appropriate boxes on the registration page. If you do opt in, you can always change your mind and inform us that you no longer want to disclose your information to new marketing partners. Simply contact our customer services department by email at [support@essayedge.com](mailto:support@essayedge.com) and request removal from our external email list or call us at 1-888-438-2633.

_Newsletter_

If a user wishes to subscribe to any of our newsletters, we ask them to register by providing their contact information (email address), geographic information (zip code), and segmentation information (high school student, parent, etc.). Newsletter recipients will also receive Company offers from time-to-time and may opt-out of these offers by using the method described above.

_Promotions, Surveys and Contests_

From time-to-time our site requests information from users via promotions, surveys or contests. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and the user therefore has a choice whether or not to disclose this information. Information requested may include contact information (such as name and shipping address), segmentation information (such as high school student, parent, etc.) and demographic information (such as zip code). Contact information will be used to process entries, send promotional material, notify the winners and award prizes. Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving use of and satisfaction with this Web site.

Please be sure to consult the official rules of any contest or sweepstakes you enter as specific data collection and usage practices may vary by contest or sweepstakes. Unless the official rules or entry instructions provide otherwise, contest or sweepstakes participants may opt-out of receiving future mailings or having their information shared with other companies by the method described above. 

_Email A Friend/Tell A Friend_

If a user elects to participate in our referral program for recruiting friends to become a customer of the site, we ask the user to provide the email address of the friend who will then receive a one-time email message. Friends recruited through this program will register with us and enjoy all of the benefits of being a user.

_Special Offers_

We send all new members a welcoming email. Established members will occasionally receive information on products, services, special deals, or a newsletter. Out of respect for the privacy of our users we present the option to not receive these types of communications. Please see description of our opt-out policy above.

**Cookies and Web Site Information**

Like most other commercial websites, we use standard "cookie" technology and web server logs to collect information about how our web site is used. Cookies are small pieces of data that are stored by your web browser on your hard drive. The cookies allow our web servers to recognize the computers used to access our websites. Cookies allow you to move from page to page on the website, by remembering the information about the entire session. 

Information gathered through cookies and by our web server logs may include the date and time of visits, the pages viewed, time spent at our Web site, and the Web sites visited just before and just after our Web site. This information is collected on an aggregate basis. None of this information is associated with you as an individual.

**Children's Data**

The Thomson Learning websites are designed for high school students, their parents, and adults seeking information on higher education. Children under 13 years of age may use these websites to get general information about higher education. However, we do not collect personal information from anyone under 13, and children under 13 may not register or conduct personalized searches. 

**How Do We Secure Information Transmissions?**

If you purchase a product from us, we will ask for a credit card number. These transactions are secured using licensed secure server software which encrypts the information you provide. 

Additionally, we periodically review our operations and business practices for compliance with corporate policies and procedures governing the security, confidentiality and quality of our information.

**Contact Us With Any Questions**

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of our websites, or your dealings with this web site, please contact the proper address below: 

Support Services  
CyberEdit  
Third Floor  
2000 Lenox Drive  
Lawrenceville, NJ 08648  

1-888-438-2633
